MOSTAFA MOAMEN

347-265-2099 | mostafammoamen@gmail.com

PROFILE

Data Science Boot-camp graduate and a Junior at Kean University who has sights on a Data Science internship position. A persistent learner who loves acquiring new skills and taking on challenges. Experienced with Excel, Python, SQL, and Tableau.

EDUCATION

(3.48 GPA)	Data Science Bachelor's Degree, Kean University, Union NJ
May 2022	Computer Science associate degree, Brookdale CC, Lincroft NJ
May 2020	Data Science Bootcamp Certificate, Rutgers, Piscataway NJ

WORK EXPERIENCE

September 2019-Present

Tennis Instructor, New Shrewsbury Racquet Club, Tinton Falls NJ

Set up a weekly schedule that work with all clients. Teach clients of all ages and skill level how to improve their game. Communicate the progress of younger students to their parents.

January 2020-Present

Tennis Proshop Owner, New Shrewsbury Racquet Club, Tinton Falls NJ

Service the racquets that come in. Bill and collect money from costumers. Help customers find the best racquet or paddle that suits them. Market our products and

services.

January 2014-2019

Restaurant Manager, Café Villa, Eatontown NJ

Opened and closed the restaurant. Coordinated with all workers to make sure everything was in order. Learned how to work under a lot of pressure and withstand the long shifts of the restaurant business.

DATA SCIENCE EXPERIENCE

Bootcamp Project:

Worked with a team to clean and manipulate tens of thousands of Amazon Products reviews and ratings to analyze the data using Pandas. We used Scikit Learn to look at the written review and predict the rating score. We used Seaborn and Matplotlib for our Visualizations.

GitHub Repository: https://github.com/mrichtmyer/AmazonProductTrends.git

Bootcamp Project:

Worked with a team of three to analyze and predict stock prices. We scraped data of the stocks using Pandas_DataReader and predicted future stock prices using Scikit Learn.

Languages and Tools:

 Python, Excel, Java, SQL, Jupyter Notebook, Google Cloud and Tableau

Data Manipulation:

 Pandas, Matplotlib, NumPy, Seaborn, and Scikit Learn